♪ DAYS PASS BY
AND MY EYES THEY DRY ♪
♪ AND I THINK THAT I'M OKAY ♪
♪ 'TILL I FIND MYSELF
IN CONVERSATION FADING AWAY ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU SMILE ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU WALK ♪
♪ THE TIME YOU TOOK ♪
♪ TO TEACH ME ALL
THAT YOU HAD TAUGHT ♪
♪ TELL ME HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO MOVE ON ♪
♪ THESE DAYS I'M BECOMING
EVERYTHING THAT I HATE ♪
♪ WISHING YOU WERE AROUND
BUT NOW IT'S TOO LATE ♪
♪ MY MIND IS A PLACE
THAT I CAN'T ESCAPE YOUR GHOST ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WISH
THAT I COULD WISH IT ALL AWAY ♪
♪ ONE MORE RAINY DAY
WITHOUT YOU ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WISH THAT I
COULD SEE YOU ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ ONE MORE RAINY DAY ♪
♪ OH I'M A WRECK
WITHOUT YOU HERE ♪
♪ YEAH I'M A WRECK
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN GONE ♪
♪ I'VE TRIED TO PUT
THIS ALL BEHIND ME ♪
♪ I THINK I WAS WRECKED
ALL ALONG ♪
♪ YEAH I'M A WRECK ♪
♪ THEY SAY THAT THE TIME
WILL HEAL IT ♪
♪ THE PAIN WILL GO AWAY ♪
♪ BUT EVERYTHING,
IT REMINDS ME OF YOU ♪
♪ AND IT COMES IN WAVES ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU LAUGH
WHEN YOUR SHOULDERS SHOOK ♪
♪ THE TIME YOU TOOK ♪
♪ TO TEACH ME ALL
THAT YOU HAD TAUGHT ♪
♪ TELL ME HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO MOVE ON ♪
♪ THESE DAYS I'M BECOMING
EVERYTHING THAT I HATE ♪
♪ WISHING YOU WERE AROUND
BUT NOW IT'S TOO LATE ♪
♪ MY MIND IS A PLACE THAT I
CAN'T ESCAPE YOUR GHOST ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WISH THAT I
COULD WISH IT ALL AWAY ♪
♪ ONE MORE RAINY DAY
WITHOUT YOU ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WISH THAT I
COULD SEE YOU ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ ONE MORE RAINY DAY ♪
♪ OH I'M A WRECK
WITHOUT YOU HERE ♪
♪ YEAH I'M A WRECK
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN GONE ♪
♪ I'VE TRIED TO PUT
THIS ALL BEHIND ME ♪
♪ I THINK I WAS WRECKED
ALL ALONG ♪
♪ THESE DAYS WHEN I'M
ON THE BRINK OF THE EDGE ♪
♪ I REMEMBER THE WORDS
THAT YOU SAID ♪
♪ REMEMBER THE LIFE YOU LED ♪
♪ YOU'D SAY OH SUCK IT ALL UP ♪
♪ DON'T GET STUCK IN THE MUD ♪
♪ THINKIN' OF THINGS
THAT YOU SHOULD HAVE DONE ♪
♪ I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN
MY LOVED ONE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN
MY LOVED ONE ♪
♪ YEAH I'M A WRECK ♪
♪ I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN
MY LOVED ONE ♪
♪ YEAH I'M A WRECK
WITHOUT YOU HERE ♪
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN GONE ♪
♪ I'VE TRIED TO PUT
THIS ALL BEHIND ME ♪
♪ I THINK I WAS WRECKED
ALL ALONG ♪
♪ YEAH I'M A WRECK ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WISH THAT I
COULD WISH IT ALL AWAY ♪
♪ ONE MORE RAINY DAY
WITHOUT YOU ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I WISH THAT I
COULD SEE YOU ONE MORE DAY ♪
♪ ONE MORE RAINY DAY ♪
[OCEAN WAVES CRASHING]
- [WOMAN'S VOICE]
WHEN TRIALS COME
THINGS THAT ARE IMPORTANT
BECOME REALLY CLEAR
[OCEAN WAVES CRASHING]